A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Catalogued Reports, Reports 11775-13948 FA739E
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accountability and effectiveness of NGO policy alliances (Reports 013920), 1994 (Box 741, Reel R-9299)
  International Workshop on NGOs and Accountability in the New World Order (1994: Manchester, England)
  Non-governmental organizations; Democratization; Sustainable development; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Economy, ecology and spirituality: toward a theory and practice of sustainability, Sept. (Reports 013921), 1993 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Economy, ecology and spirituality
  Sustainable development; Asian NGO Coalition for Agrarian Reform and Rural Development; IRED Asia (Organization); People-Centered Development Forum; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Poverty, emerging literacy, and school readiness among young children in the U.S.: analyses of data from the National Household Education Survey School Readiness Component, Dec. (Reports 013922), 1995 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Based on results of a telephone survey conducted in 1993, geared to answering 10 major questions several which follow: 1. How many of today's preschool and early elementary school children in the United States come from families whose annual incomes are b
  09351300
  Westat, Inc.
  Education, Preschool -- United States; Literacy; Poor children -- United States; Columbia University. National Center for Children in Poverty; Westat, Inc.
- Descriptive information about preschoolers and early elementary students in poverty in the U.S.: analyses of data from the National Household Education Survey School Readiness Component, Dec. (Reports 013923), 1995 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Poses and answers the following questions: Which subgroups of children are most likely to be poor? What does the population of poor pre-schoolers and early elementary school children look like? What types of poverty-related experiences did poor early elem
- A note on NGOs and policy influence, Sept. (Reports 013924), 1992 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Non-governmental organizations; Government policy; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Working more effectively with nongovernmental organizations (Reports 013925), 1991 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Non-governmental organizations; Sustainable development; World Bank; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Report on visit to Irian Jaya as the guest of YPMD (Reports 013926), 1989 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Sustainable development -- Indonesia -- Irian Jaya; Yayasan Pengembangan Masyarakat Desa Irian Jaya; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Inter-regional Consultation on People's Participation in Environmentally Sustainable Development, Makati, Metro Manila, Philippines, 6-10 June 1989, 1989. (Reports 013927) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Inter-regional Consultation on People's Participation in Environmentally Sustainable Development (1989: Manila, Philippines)
  Sustainable development; Asian NGO Organization for Agrarian Reform and Rural Development; Environment Liaison Centre; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Civil society, the state, and roles of NGOs, Aug. (Reports 013928), 1991 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  IDR working paper;no. 9
  Civil society -- Developing Countries; Non-governmental organizations -- Developing countries; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Politics of life: Knowledge, science and education in the contemporary world, Sept. (Reports 013929), 1991 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Economic development; World politics; Civilization; Quality of life; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Multiparty cooperation for development in Asia (Reports 013930), 1992 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Poverty -- Asia; Non-governmental organizations -- Asia; International cooperation; Institute for Development Research (Boston, Mass.); Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- Multiparty collaboration for development in Asia, Feb. (Reports 013931), 1992 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Poverty -- Asia; Non-governmental organizations -- Asia; International cooperation; Society for Participatory Research in Asia; Institute for Development Research (Boston, Mass.); Synergos Institute; Institute for Development Research, Inc.
- A profile of research libraries in Sub-Saharan Africa: acquisitions, outreach, and infrastructure (Reports 013932), 1993 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Africa and the Middle East; Africa and the Middle East/Eastern & Southern Africa
  09400320
  American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS)
  Research libraries -- Africa, Sub-Saharan; American Association for the Advancement of Science. Sub-Saharan Africa Program; American Association for the Advancement of Science
- Electronic networking in Africa: advancing science and technology for development: Workshop on Science and Technology Communication Networks in Africa, August 27-29, 1992, Nairobi, Kenya (Reports 013933) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Workshop on Science and Technology Communication Networks in Africa Nairobi, Kenya) (1992:
  Communication in science -- Congresses -- Abstracts; Computer networks -- Africa -- Congresses -- Abstracts; Communication -- Network analysis (Planning) -- Congresses -- Abstracts; Communication of technical information -- Africa -- Congresses -- Abstracts; African Academy of Sciences; American Association for the Advancement of Science. Sub-Saharan Africa Program; American Association for the Advancement of Science
- Projeto Tucuma, planificacao sanitaria: sumario Summary of sanitary planning for the Tucuma project (Reports 013934), 1977 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  "The Tucuma project calls for the planned resettlement of 2,921 families (between 15,000 and 20,000 people) in an area of 4,000 square kilometres in the municipality of Sao Felix do Xingu, in the state of Para, over a period of six years. During this time
  07300514
  Federal University of Para
  Summary of sanitary planning for the Tucuma project
  Public health -- Amazon River Region; Fundação Laura de Andrade; Universidade Federal do Pará; Universidade Federal do Pará
- Preventing damaged lives: a family support system for Arizona's children, Sept. (Reports 013935), 1990 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  08900145
  Tucson Community Foundation, Inc.
  Children -- Arizona -- Social conditions; Children's Action Alliance; Arizona Community Foundation; Tucson Community Foundation.; Children's Behavioral Health Council (Ariz.); Arizona. Department of Health Services; Tucson Community Foundation, Inc.
- The Ockenden Venture: the Thai Payap Project, Nan.: CHANIP: the Community Highland Agriculture and Nutrition Improvement Programme: report for period 1st April to 30th (Reports 013936-001), 1991 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  09051265
  The Ockenden Venture
  Agriculture -- Thailand; Forests and forestry -- Thailand; Ockenden Venture; Community Highland Agriculture and Nutrition Improvement Programme.; The Ockenden Venture
- Schooling and the experience of adolescents in Kenya (Reports 013936-002), 1997 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  09600409
  The Population Council, Inc.
  Teenagers -- Kenya; Education -- Kenya; Sex instruction -- Kenya; Population Council; The Population Council, Inc.
- Summary of proceedings of Workshop on Local Government held on January 31, 1995, Dhaka, Bangladesh (Reports 013937) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  09400958
  Centre for Analysis and Choice
  Workshop on local government;Local government
  Workshop on Local Government (1995: Dhaka, Bangladesh)
  Local government -- Bangladesh; Centre for Analysis and Choice (Dhaka, Bangladesh); Centre for Analysis and Choice
- Summary of proceedings of Workshop on "Trade Unions and Privatization" held on April 1, 1995, Dhaka, Bangladesh (Reports 013938) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Workshop on Trade Unions and Privatization;Trade Unions and Privatization
  Workshop on "Trade Unions and Privatization" (1995: Dhaka, Bangladesh)
  Trade unions -- Bangladesh; Privatization -- Bangladesh; Centre for Analysis and Choice (Dhaka, Bangladesh); Centre for Analysis and Choice
- Summary of proceedings of Workshop on Women's Representation in Parliament held on June 4, 1995, Dhaka, Bangladesh (Reports 013939) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Workshop on women's representation in Parliament;Women's Representation in Parliament
  Workshop on Women's Representation in Parliament(1995: Dhaka, Bangladesh)
  Women in politics -- Bangladesh; Centre for Analysis and Choice (Dhaka, Bangladesh); Centre for Analysis and Choice
- Summary of proceedings of Workshop on Legislation by Ordinance held on July 15, 1995, Dhaka, Bangladesh (Reports 013940) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Workshop on Legislation by Ordinance;Legislation by Ordinance
  Workshop on Legislation by Ordinance (1995: Dhaka, Bangladesh)
  Representative government and representation -- Bangladesh; Legislation -- Bangladesh; Centre for Analysis and Choice (Dhaka, Bangladesh); Centre for Analysis and Choice
- Summary of proceedings of Workshop on Code of Conduct for Elections held on October 10, 1995, Dhaka, Bangladesh (Reports 013941) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Workshop on Code of Conduct for Elections;Code of Conduct for Elections
  Workshop on Code of Conduct for Elections (1995: Dhaka, Bangladesh)
  Elections -- Bangladesh; Centre for Analysis and Choice (Dhaka, Bangladesh); Centre for Analysis and Choice
- Rickshaw pullers in Dhaka City: Their problems and their perception about certain common issues, Aug. (Reports 013943), 1995 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  CAC poll paper;1
  Rickshaw men -- Bangladesh -- Dhaka (Bangladesh); Working poor -- Bangladesh; Caste -- India; Centre for Analysis and Choice (Dhaka, Bangladesh); Ford Foundation. Rural Poverty and Resources; Centre for Analysis and Choice
- Mujer y derecho de familia = Women and right of family, 1992. (Reports 013944) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  09550583
  Corporation for Legal Training for Citizenship and Democracy
  Women and right of family
  Women's rights -- Chile; Family -- Chile; Instituto de Formación Jurídica para la Acción (Chile); Instituto Latinoamericano de Doctrina y Estudios Sociales; Corporation for Legal Training for Citizenship and Democracy
- Derechos legales de la mujer trabajadora = Legal rights of working women, 1992. (Reports 013945) (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Legal rights of working women
  Women -- Employment -- Chile -- Legal status, laws, etc.; Women's rights -- Chile; Instituto de Formación Jurídica para la Acción (Chile); Instituto Latinoamericano de Doctrina y Estudios Sociales; Corporation for Legal Training for Citizenship and Democracy
- Report to the Ford Foundation regarding the Institute of International Education, May 2 (Reports 013946), 1995 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Education; Institute of International Education -- Evaluation
- The Ford Foundation, the Social Science Research Council: Evaluation of its activities in Latin America, Africa and Asia (Reports 013947), 1996 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Three reports evaluating activities of the SSRC in Latin America, Africa and Asia.
  Social sciences -- Study and teaching -- Latin America; Social sciences -- Study and teaching -- Africa; Social sciences -- Study and teaching -- Asia; Social Science Research Council; Social Science Research Council
- Burma opportunities Memo, 9 (Reports 013948), 1988 (Box 742, Reel R-9299)
  Developing Countries Program/BangladeshNG
  Community development -- Burma; Economic development -- Burma; Ford Foundation. Developing Countries